(Penny:)Well, some people just can't handle
that kind of relationship.
(Sheldon:)Can you?
(Penny:)Excuse me?
(Sheldon:)Are you able to have sex with men without
developing an emotional attachment?
Sheldon, I really don't wanna
talk about this with you.
(Sheldon:)Is this conversation
making you uncomfortable?
(Penny:)Of course it's making me uncomfortable.
Can't you tell?
(Sheldon:)I really have no idea.
(Sheldon:)I don't particularly excel
at reading facial expressions...
(Penny:)I'm uncomfortable, Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)Thank you, that's very helpful.
All right,
where are these amazing shrimp?
(Leonard:)Behold.
Seriously?
You think this is the size of a baby's arm?
(Raj:)A little baby.
(Howard:)I'm going back to the room.
(Michaela(arriving):)Boy, would it maybe kill them
to put out a nice brisket?